<resources>
    <string name="app_name">View Demonstrations Lab</string>
    <string name="wow">Wow!</string>
    <string name="message">Welcome.</string>
    <string name="the_tra_phrase">Are you having fun?</string>
    <string name="the_answer">I certainly hope so!</string>
    <string name="long_text">Chapter 1 - Time to Leave
	“How long will it be before the train gets here?” asked Noeva.
	“Only 10 minutes!” responded Mila, looking at the train arrival time on her phone.
	“Remember, you two, use your phones sparingly,” said Mila and Noeva’s mother.
	“We know,” sighed Mila. “You don’t have to tell us more than once.”
	“You’re still looking at your phone, though,” responded the mother. “I mean, if you want me to stop telling you this you should probably stop looking at your phone.”
	“I was looking at the train arrival time!” complained Mila. “Plus, how else am I gonna be able to ignore my cousins?”
	Noeva giggled.
	The mother sighed and said, “Look, I know they’re quite a lot to handle, but you should still interact with them and get to know them well.”
	“For the entire summer! Tell me something that’s not impossible,” groaned Mila.
	Suddenly, the group heard the piercing sound of a train traveling down the tracks.
	“The train is here!” shouted Noeva. “You were lying about the time!”
	“Let’s get a seat,” said Mila.
	The three went on the train.
	“When will they get here?” asked LN. “When will they get here, when will they get here, when will they get here!”
	“In precisely 75 days,” swiftly responded Antoine.
	“No one needs your sarcasm,” said Lia.
	“I’m being one hundred percent serious, what are you talking about?” responded Antoine.
	“How are you my older brother,” sighed Lia. “I expect such ridiculousness from middle schoolers, but you?”
	“You know me well enough now that the answer is yes,” replied Antoine.
	A sharp, loud sound was heard in the next room, something like a table crashing.
	“What did you do this time, LN?” asked Antoine.
	“This time, I did nothing, ” said LN, “because it wasn’t me.”
	Lia laughed. “So we’re supposed to believe this is different from every other time?”
	The Chaquet mom suddenly appeared next to the group of three. “What is this ruckus? Mademoiselle Lia, have anything to say?”
	“What makes you think it’s me when it’s always LN?” asked Lia.
	“We know half the things we’ve blamed on Cher LN have actually been you,” responded the mom. “What do you have to say for yourself?”
	Antoine, who had quickly went to the room to see the situation, shouted, “There’s a rat in the room!”
	Everyone was running amok at the sight of the rat, until Lia got her mousetrap that she had saved a month ago for such a situation.
	“Where did you get that mousetrap, Mademoiselle?” shouted the mom.
	“My friend gave it to me cause of the rat infestation in the area,” responded Lia.
	“What rat infestation?” asked Antoine. “Besides, why would a mousetrap be any good for catching a rat? It’s in the name. Mouse trap. Not rat trap.”
	“But it still works!” shouted Lia.
	“Okay, Mademoiselle Lia is technically right about the rat infestation,” said the mom. “However, Monsieur Antoine, you are correct in saying that a mouse trap is not the best solution.”
	“I’ll get the cheese from the cabinet!” shouted LN.
	“What a catastrophe!” exclaimed the mom. “Your cousins are about to here any minute and we’re shouting about some crazy rat.”
	Everyone stops at the doorbell being rung.
	“They’re here!” shouted LN.
	“Without telling us? Ridiculous,” said Antoine.
	The mom opened the door, muttered a few incomprehensible words, then closed the door.
	“What was that?” asked Lia.
	“It was just a delivery,” responded the mom. “Your dad said he would warn us when they got to the train station.”
	Everyone went back upstairs to see what had happened to the mouse.
	“Oh, looks like there was a hole in the wall,” said the mom. “Time to patch that up, I suppose.”
	A loud ding was heard.
	“For goodness sake, why was that so loud?” inquired the mom. “Cher LN, did you use my phone again?”
	“I wouldn’t if you would just buy me one!” yelled LN.
	“My goodness, you’re not old enough yet!” said the mom. “The entire point of this trip is that you all won’t use your phone.”
	“And talk to some old woman who no one knows,” said LN.
	“I already told you,” said the mom. “She’s-”
	“Our and our cousins’ great grandpa’s first cousin once removed,” said the three Chaquet siblings in unison.
	“Or in other terms, our grandpa’s second cousin,” added Antoine.
	“See? That isn’t so distant,” said the mom. “Only a few words to say.”
	“A few words? Yes,” said Antoine. “However, it’s still quite distant!”
	The doorbell rang once again.
	“Now it’s them,” said the mom.
	The family collectively opened the door and welcomed the cousins in.
	“All our suitcases are ready!” exclaimed the mom.
	“A rat came in the house!” shouted LN.
	“For goodness sake, please keep your mouth shut Cher LN,” said the mom.
	“Why does it matter? Are we supposed to keep secrets from our dear wonderful cousins?” sarcastically asked Antoine.
	“My oh my,” said Mila and Noeva’s mom. “I can’t wait to get to Massachusetts.”
	Mila and Noeva just stood silent with a look of dread on their faces.
	“We’re gonna have an absolutely abysmal summer aren’t we,” sighed Mila.
	“Oh, always the one to complain,” said Lia. “What a spoilsport.”
	“Well, come on!” shouted the Chaquet mom. “We’d like to at least leave before school starts!”
</string>
</resources>
